Inventory of the Episcopal Church, Diocese of Wyoming, 1883-2005
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Series VIII. Topics, 1898-1996
  - College of St. John, the Evangelist, Articles of Incorporation, 1938-1939 (Box 152)
  - RESTRICTED- Consecration Preparations and Materials, 1969-1987 (Box 152)
  - Constitution and Canons, 1925-1937 (Box 165)
  - Constitution and Canons, 1937-1938 (Box 152)
  - Conventions and Convocations, 1909-1973 (Box 153, 165, 192)
  - Council of Advice, 1921-1952 (Box 165, 192)
  - Council of Advice, 1941-1967 (Box 153)
  - Confirmations, 1909-1947 (Box 154)
  - Confirmations, 1928-1972 (Box 155)
  - Confirmations, 1931-1976 (Box 156)
  - RESTRICTED- Confirmations and Baptisms, 1977-1996 (Box 157)
  - RESTRICTED- Crusade for the 80's Fund Drive, circa 1981 (Box 158)
  - Episcopal Church Women, 1932-1980 (Box 153, 159-160)
  - Executive Council Minutes, 1948-1969 (Box 160)
  - Historical Papers and Teaching Materials, 1945-1966 (Box 160)
  - History- Episcopal Church in Wyoming, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 21-23)
  - History- Episcopal Church in Wyoming, 1951 (Box 35, Folder 1-4)
  - Indian Reservation Work, 1911-1968 (Box 161-164)
  - Investment File, 1936-1955 (Box 192)
  - Letters Dimissory, 1932-1973 (Box 165)
  - Meeteetse, Specifications for Episcopal Church, 1905 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Office Files, circa 1943 (Box 165)
  - Parish Register- St. Helen's, Crowheart, WY, 1942-1967 (Box 182)
  - Property and Estate Files, 1918-1956 (Box 165-166)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Contracts, 1929 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Correspondence, Advertising, 1927-1928 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Correspondence, Atwater-Kent Contest, 1927 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Correspondence, Beginning of Radio Station, 1922-1924 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Correspondence, Book and Magazine Reviews, 1923-1929 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Correspondence, Closing Days, 1927-1928 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Correspondence, Closing Out of Station, 1929-1930 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Correspondence, Equipment Repair or Equipment, 1926-1929 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Correspondence, Licenses, 1923-1928 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Correspondence, Licensing by American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers, 1928-1929 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Correspondence, Listener Reception, 1922-1928 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1922-1928 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Correspondence, Missing Persons Broadcasts, 1927-1929 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Correspondence, Mountain States Telephone Patent, 1924-1928 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Correspondence, Positions Wanted, 1927-1928 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Correspondence, Programming, 1925-1929 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Correspondence, Radio Protective Association, 1928 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Correspondence, Union Pacific Train Wreck, 1926-1927 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Correspondence, Wishing to Purchase Station, 1928 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Invoices for Equipment, 1922 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Licenses, 1922-1929 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Photographs, 1925-1928 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Publications, Advertisements for Equipment, 1920-1922 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Publications, Government Regulations, 1919-1928 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Radio Station KFBU- Writings About, 1971 and undated (Box 36, Folder 17-20)
  - Register of Church Services, Approximately 1915-1969 (Box 167)
  - Saint Matthews Cathedral, 1913-1968 (Box 37, Folder 1-6)
  - Scrapbook- Newspaper Clippings, 1898-1899 (Box 38)
  - Scrapbook- Newspaper Clippings, 1911-1914 (Box 181)
  - Scrapbook- Newspaper Clippings, 1918-1921 (Box 182)
  - Sherwood Hall, 1938-1942 (Box 168-169)
  - RESTRICTED- Search Committee for Special Election Convention, 1976-1977 (Box 170)
  - Testimonials- Election of Bishops, 1968-1969 (Box 169)
  - Wyoming History, 1902-1940 (Box 192)
- Series IX. Churches, 1916-1989
  This series contains correspondence and other information about individual churches in Wyoming. Churches are arranged by town/city. Similar materials can also be found in the Bishops' office files series.
  - B-C, 1916-1984 (Box 171)
  - C-E, 1921-1982 (Box 172)
  - E-G, 1916-1982 (Box 173)
  - G-L, 1921-1989 (Box 174)
  - L-P, 1920-1982 (Box 175)
  - P-S, 1918-1989 (Box 176)
  - S-W, 1916-1989 (Box 177)
  - Hanna, 1940-1979 (Box 178)
  - La Barge, 1943-1948 (Box 178)
  - Lander, 1919-1940 (Box 178)
  - Laramie, 1943-1946 (Box 178)
  - Rock River, 1923-1965 (Box 178)
- Series X. Publications, 1894-2004
  Contains newsletters and other publications covering activities, news, information, and meetings of the Episcopal Church of Wyoming. Includes individual written histories of some churches in Wyoming. There are also pamphlets and other publications from the national level.
  - Journal of Annual Conventions/ Missionary District of Wyoming Journal of Convocation, 1897-1980 (Box 91)
  - Journal of Annual Conventions/ Missionary District of Wyoming Journal of Convocation, 1932-1979 (Box 92)
  - Journal of Annual Conventions/ Missionary District of Wyoming Journal of Convocation, 1983-2004 (Box 93)
  - Miscellaneous National Publications, 1898-1983 (Box 94)
  - Miscellaneous Wyoming Publications, 1919-1976 (Box 94, 191)
  - Pamphlets, Ab - Bu, circa 1925 (Box 17)
  - Pamphlets, Ca - Co, 1855-1927 (Box 18)
  - Pamphlets, Co - Di, undated (Box 19)
  - Pamphlets, Di - Ex, undated (Box 20)
  - Pamphlets, Fa - Gu, circa 1920 (Box 21)
  - Pamphlets, Ha - Io, circa 1920 (Box 22)
  - Pamphlets, Ja - Ma, undated (Box 23)
  - Pamphlets, Me - Mi, circa 1920 (Box 24)
  - Pamphlets, Mi - O, 1885-1932 (Box 25)
  - Pamphlets, Pa - Pu, undated (Box 26)
  - Pamphlets, Re - Si, undated (Box 27)
  - Pamphlets, Si - Ty, undated (Box 28)
  - Pamphlets, U - Y, undated (Box 29)
  - Preconvention Meeting/ Reports, 1984-2004 (Box 95)
  - Primary Bible Story, 1953-1955 (Box 95)
  - Primary Child, 1951-1953 (Box 95)
  - Spirit of Wyoming, 1985-2001 (Box 95)
  - Spirit of Wyoming, 1989-1994 (Box 191)
  - Spirit of Wyoming, 1993-1989 (Box 96)
  - Wyoming Churchmen, 1894, 1915, 1917 (Box 191)
  - Wyoming Churchmen, 1917-1968 (Box 96)
  - Wyoming Churchmen, 1933-1961 (Box 97)
  - Wyoming Churchmen, 1964-1984 (Box 184)
  - Wyoming Churchmen, 1967-1988 (Box 191)
  - Wyoming Churchmen, undated (Box 183)
- Series XI. Audio Visual Records, 1915-1989 (Most materials undated)
  Contains photographs, negatives, slides, and videocassettes of clergy, church activities, churches and towns, unidentified individuals, ranches, and schools. Also includes transparencies of a presentation on growing the membership.
  - Bishop Thornberry Consecration Film, 1969 (Box 190)
  - Cathedral Home for Children, Laramie, WY Photos, undated (Box 29)
  - Ft. Laramie Project- plats, maps, poster, approximately 1915-1920 (Box 180)
  - Grace Episcopal Cathedral, Topeka, KS, undated (Box 29)
  - Motion Picture Film, undated (Box 188-189)
  - Phonograph Records, undated (Box 190)
  - Photo Albums, Slides, Transparencies, VHS tape, Approximately 1966-1989 (Box 98)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 99-100, 180)
  - Photo Albums, undated (Box 183)
  - Nitrate Negatives- Ziegler, undated (Box 194)
- Series XII. Standing Committee Records, 1883-1987
  RESTRICTED- Materials in this series are restricted for 70 years from their creation date. See restriction note for Class A Restricted Records (above) for details. Box #181 is unrestricted. Includes meeting minutes and correspondence.
  - Standing Committee Minutes, 1883-1937 (Box 181)
  - RESTRICTED- Standing Committee Files, 1964-1987 (Box 179)
- Series XIII. Remarriage Files, 1963-1998
  RESTRICTED- Materials in this series are restricted for 70 years from their creation date. See restriction note for Class A Restricted Records (above) for details. Contains correspondence from divorced people requesting remarriage. Files dated after 1969 filed alphabetically by divorcee's last name.
  - RESTRICTED- Remarriage Files, 1963, 1967, 1968-1969 (Box 101)
  - RESTRICTED- Remarriage Files, 1964 (Box 108)
  - RESTRICTED- Remarriage Files, 1965 (Box 192)
  - RESTRICTED- Remarriage Files, A-C, 1970-1989 (Box 101)
  - RESTRICTED- Remarriage Files, C-I, 1970-1989 (Box 102)
  - RESTRICTED- Remarriage Files, J-M, 1970-1989 (Box 103)
  - RESTRICTED- Remarriage Files, N-T, 1970-1989 (Box 104)
  - RESTRICTED- Remarriage Files, U-Z, 1970-1989 (Box 105)
  - RESTRICTED- Remarriage Files, 1986-1987 (Box 105)
  - RESTRICTED- Remarriage Files, A-C, 1990-1992 (Box 105)
  - RESTRICTED- Remarriage Files, D-W, 1990-1992 (Box 106)
  - RESTRICTED- Remarriage Files, A-R, 1993 (Box 106)
  - RESTRICTED- Remarriage Files, S-W, 1993 (Box 107)
  - RESTRICTED- Remarriage Files, 1994-1996 (Box 107)
  - RESTRICTED- Remarriage Files, 1997-1998 (Box 108)
- Series XIV. Personnel Records, 1944-2005
  RESTRICTED- Materials in this series are restricted for 70 years from their creation date. See restriction note for Class A Records (above) for details.
  - RESTRICTED- Personnel Records, 1944-1946 (Box 109)
  - RESTRICTED- Personnel Records, 1947 (Box 192)
  - RESTRICTED- Personnel Records, 1949-1965 (Box 193)
  - RESTRICTED- Personnel Records, 1956-1965 (Box 109-110)
  - RESTRICTED- Personnel Records, 1966-1967 (Box 110-111)
  - RESTRICTED- Personnel Records, 1968 (Box 111-112)
  - RESTRICTED- Personnel Records, A-C, 1970-2001 (Box 112)
  - RESTRICTED- Personnel Records, C-G, 1973-2005 (Box 113)
  - RESTRICTED- Personnel Records, G-J, 1972-2004 (Box 114)
  - RESTRICTED- Personnel Records, J-M, 1979-2005 (Box 115)
  - RESTRICTED- Personnel Records, M-P, 1971-2002 (Box 116)
  - RESTRICTED- Personnel Records, Q-S, 1977-2002 (Box 117)
  - RESTRICTED- Personnel Records, T-Z, 1971-2001 (Box 118)